The good. The bad. The Satanic.
Ghost Town is a horror, western, crime film directed by Richard Governor.
Deputy Langley tracks a kidnapped girl to an abandoned ghost town.
However, the town is not abandoned, but haunted by the spirits of an outlaw, Devlin, and his gang, who
hold the equally deceased townspeople hostage until the outlaws can be killed by a lawman.
Langley, played by Franc Luz.
Kate, played by Catherine Hickland.
Devlin, played by Jimmie F. Skaggs.
Dealer, played by Bruce Glover.
Blacksmith, played by Zitto Kazann.
Etta, played by Laura Schaefer.
Ghost Town is a 1988 American Western horror film directed by Richard McCarthy (under the
pseudonym Richard Governor) and starring Franc Luz and Catherine Hickland.
Based on a story by David Schmoeller, it follows a sheriff who finds himself amongst
the dead residents of a ghost town while searching for a missing woman.
The film was one of the last to be released by producer
Charles Band's production company Empire Pictures.
The film explores themes of outlaw, curse, shootout.
The tone is dark.